last week we cover the PT or a couple
Ultima septimana de hora tegimus aut duobus TP
weeks ago P camera yes yes so we have an
P weeks abhinc quod sic camera est non habere, quod sic
update on it about an adapter yeah do
an update de ea semper nibh ut faciam yeah
you remember we I showed what I soldered
meministis enim et ostendit quod solidantur
myself so we got this p OE adapter that
haec ego sic obtinuit œ nibh
means power over ethernet so we've got
Comperto itaque potestatem significat ethernet
this great PTZ camera all these short
omnia denique tanti diam PTZ
forms right great tech show all these
omnes hae formae maximae Tech
short forms p TZ is pan tilt zoom so you
p sit formae brevi TZ Pan te equum et Zoom
think about a camera that can pan left
qui sinistra pars sit cogitare de camera
and right tilt up and down and zoom so
Retrahe ergo et jus et sternent
in and out so PTZ camera that's what it
Sic et illud quod in diam PTZ
represents it means you can digitally
auditus est potestis digitally
through an app or through a program on
propter quod et per progressio in app
your computer a web browser you can
Vos can pasco telam in computatrum tuum
control the positioning in the zoom of
zoom in in positioning de control
our camera it's great but one of the
quin de camera nostra est
things with it is that you've got to
quae sunt apud te est conplexio est
have not only Ethernet or Wi-Fi network
Aer enim non solum non Wi-FI network
connectivity but you also have to have
sed etiam ut habeat connectivity
power to it right and so that means this
ita ut hoc ius
wall wart that's got to be plugged in
ut clavus in murum 'got ad inplenda
and then plugged into the camera well I
et tunc in camera tam me SUPERGESTUS
came up with this with this little
hoc cum eo venerunt
dongle that would convert power over
dongle quod potestatem ac novandum
ethernet from yes from a surveillance
Etiam a ethernet de custodia circumdant
camera of all things okay to work with
purus diam omnia operari
the PTZ camera we were reviewing which
quod nos recensentes PTZ ad cameram
you can find out more about and actually
Vos can expiscor magis circa tendens, ultro
get the the device cat v dot TV slash
TV fabrica quod dat v cattus adepto a VULNUS
PTZ but then one of my friends brett he
Brett et PTZ sed tunc unus ex amicis meis epularer
found a device on amazon which we've now
in fabrica Ive 'invenitur in Amazon qua nunc
added to that link so you can pick it up
addita sunt quae possis colligere
directly because not everybody has the
directe, quia non habet in omnibus
NAD soldering skills of Robbie you know
Glutathione S solidatorium Robbie artes et scitis
if I am you've seen my soldering skills
Si ego te vidi meum artes solidatorium
loose definition you have okay oh I mean
utinam ut bene sit tibi in definitione solutam
mad like you know Mad Hatter okay no I
insaniam convertunt sicut scitis neque ego bene Mad Hatter
saw in a matter of seven days you like
Vidi te sub septem
improved by like a hundred percent she's
quasi ab ipsa suus 'melius centum percent
the kindest person in the world yeah you
fiatque mitissimo homini in hoc mundo non yeah
started from the bottom now you're here
incepit ab imo iam tu hic,
started from the bottom now here so
sic hie nunc coepi ab imo
Brett found an adapter on Amazon that is
Brett inventus est super Amazon semper nibh ut
exactly what I created but it's like two
Ego prorsus quid creatum, sed est quasi duo
bucks the one I made cost six bucks
Et factum est cost illos leones, quos ad sex illos leones,
and the one I made is this like
et quis est iste similis factus sum
three-inch dong 4 inch dongle this one
IV digiti pollicis dongle quod inter three-dong
is just like a little tip that you just
apice parum iustus est sicut
plug on to the adapter vulva so here you
ita hic ad obturaculum nibh vulvae
go it exists but if you if you do like
ire libet esse si feceritis
size to price ratio it's a better value
Ratio est magis mole et pretium valorem
for girls so how many dollars per end of
Quot puellae pupa per finem
the adapter so this thing is is going to
ita futurum est nibh
allow you to use power over ethernet on
Aer in potestatem concessit utendi
the PTZ camera that we reviewed right
ut recte stent in camera PTZ
and it's like it's all pre fin dangled
Sicut et prae fi Tota dangled
so you don't have to be a master
ita non esse dominum
soldering guru like me is so sarcastic
Guru solidatorium ut mecum sit et dicaces
watch that episode check it out how many
quae res quot coerceret vigilate
episodes have I messed up soldering on
in Episode ego messed usque soudando
[Music]
[Musica]
[Applause]
[Plausus]